[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v1",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_10",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Footwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_Morgaine_p2v1_01_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p6",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "earringedengrovet5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p10",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Chestwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p7",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Handwear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Galahad_p3a",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionFamilyWardAngryEarthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p6v2",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT4_Headgear_50",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_complete_available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p14",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Chestwear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p15",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 15,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v2",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_MSQ2EG_GuardiansSatchel",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3",
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_alt",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v2",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_alt_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_MSQ2EG_GuardiansSatchel",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_complete_available_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3",
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"Task": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99E_Yash_p3",
		"AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_objective_title",
		"Description": "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_objective_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_complete_available_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3"
	}
]